Who's a big believer in momentum I think the hardest part is just getting started.
Once you get started though you start getting momentum.
Momentum is that energy that keeps moving you forward.
It's so important in your efforts to pass the exam to pass the PMP that you find B.M. that you find
a way to keep going to find some daily time to involve in studying for your PMP.
We also need to look at the big picture here.
This is not going to last forever like a project.
It's not going to go on and on and on forever.
I've met people or talked to people that have taken you know the whole year from when their application
was approved to actually go sit for the exam.
Frankly not a good idea.
Compress that compacted it rather than stretch out your misery over a year and to get disconnected with
this information over a year.
Sooner is better.
And as we talked about earlier and as you did in one of your assignments was to create a steady strategy
if your goal is a year to pass this exam.
By the time you get to month nine or 10 look at how much time has passed and are going to lose touch
with this information.
Like most things in life the longer you wait the worse it's going to be.
So you really want to come back that effort by momentum compact the effort be dedicated and get it done.
I have confidence that you can do this.
I know that you can do this so find effort find the time find the energy create momentum stay in this
course you're doing a great job you've already covered a lot of material.
And now we're going to be starting to get into the more specific knowledge areas as we work our way
through the Pinback guy.
So I have confidence that you can do this.
Keep moving forward and I'll see you in the next lecture.